<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollingApp</string>
    <string name="article_title">The Onion</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Something About The Way Society Was Exposed As Complete Illusion Over Past Year Really Getting Man Down Today</string>
    <string name="article_text">Unable to shake off an overall negative feeling he couldn’t attribute to anything in particular, local man Paul Carpenter
        confirmed Monday that something about the way society was exposed as a complete illusion over the past year was really getting him down today.
        “Maybe it’s just quarantine talking, but the reality dawning on me that American life is a fundamentally hollow cesspool of spectacle and misery
        is really bumming me out lately,” said Carpenter, adding that he had the vague idea that living in a social system based on brutal competition that
        made all human relationships transactional and perverted the very idea of community might have something to do with it. “I can’t put my finger on it,
        but maybe I’m just really tired of the coronavirus pandemic, which wasn’t mishandled as some people say but in fact shown to be rationally handled by
        a group of insulated wealthy individuals who can pursue their greedy desires with the full knowledge that a vast percentage of Americans are
        economically superfluous and thus willing to fight among themselves for scraps? On the other hand, though, maybe it’s the stress of a news cycle in
        which people from both political parties are invested in a series of increasingly baroque conspiracy theories guided by the grotesque and increasingly
        obvious lies we tell ourselves about American exceptionalism that’s making me feel kind of sad. There’s just this nagging feeling I have that it became
        very clear over the past 12 months that the basic building blocks of society are crumbling and there is absolutely no plan for changing anything at any
        level to avoid plunging the vast majority of humanity into cycles of ever-worsening suffering and violence. Maybe it’s just that being fundamentally
        powerless and living among other similarly disenfranchised, surveilled, and downtrodden people have made me feel completely alienated from any kind of
        community at all, or maybe I just need to get more sleep.”
        \n
        Carpenter added that he did plan to address the way he’d been feeling lately, perhaps by tuning out of the news
        and letting other people who weren’t ever even afforded the option to believe in the illusions of American society
        figure out what to do, or by trying to <b>exercise</b> <i>more</i>.
        \n
        https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ
    </string>
</resources>